<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Alquin &#8211; Getting To The Top!</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 19:37:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.9</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2016/12/24/hello-world/</link>
		<comments>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2016/12/24/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 01:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alquin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/?p=1</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2016/12/24/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Case of the Missing Consul</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/26/missingconsul/</link>
		<comments>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/26/missingconsul/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 21:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kim Cooper]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[location tag]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.insroland.org/?p=600</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve discovered another mysterious disappearance tied to the Cecil Hotel. This one somehow eluded all previous archival searches, and it&#8217;s quite an odd and interesting case. I call it The Case of the Missing Consul. Around noon on December 31, 1947, Alexander M. Galbraith, 50, stepped out of the office where he had served for &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/26/missingconsul/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Case of the Missing Consul"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve discovered another mysterious disappearance tied to the Cecil Hotel. This one somehow eluded all previous archival searches, and it&#8217;s quite an odd and interesting case. I call it The Case of the Missing Consul.</p>
<p><a title="Galbraith feel grave concern over missing headline by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8516677520/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8240/8516677520_b6f9a18a6a_o.png" alt="Galbraith feel grave concern over missing headline" width="145" height="61" /></a></p>
<p>Around noon on December 31, 1947, Alexander M. Galbraith, 50, stepped out of the office where he had served for the past four years as the British Consul for Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, and vanished. His daughter Jean, who was his secretary, said he&#8217;d been brooding about the possibility of losing his position to one of the career diplomats who&#8217;d been freed up by the end of the war. He was right to worry. That very morning, he&#8217;d been informed that his services were no longer needed. The reason given was that, though Scottish-born, he was a naturalized American.</p>
<p>Galbraith, who&#8217;d been a WW1 flying ace and had a fiery reputation, was incensed. He was passionate about his position, giving pro-British speeches to local men&#8217;s clubs, dedicating long hours to aiding war brides whose American grooms had abandoned them. And now some bureaucrat was going to take his place? It was too much for him to stand.</p>
<p>On New Years Day, Deputy Coroner Ken O&#8217;Toole said Galbraith had come in, asking about a pair of missing spectacles. But a search of the neighborhood came up empty. A Pullman porter saw a photograph of the missing man, and told police he was certain he&#8217;d served him on a train bound for Chicago. Chicago authorities were alerted, but Galbraith was nowhere to be found. Searches in Washington and Cleveland also turned up nothing.</p>
<p>His wife and daughters were frantic. Weeks passed with no word. The shame of losing his job must have been too much. Had Galbraith killed himself?</p>
<p>He had not.</p>
<p>On January 27, 1948, Galbraith sent a telegram to George B. Stelluto, proprietor of The Green Grill near the Pittsburgh morgue, asking for a loan of $50. Stelluto, a friend, went to the police.</p>
<p><a title="former Greens Grill no Common Plea 310 Ross Street Pittsburgh Google Street View copy by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8516686130/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8087/8516686130_c7bc50c737.jpg" alt="former Greens Grill no Common Plea 310 Ross Street Pittsburgh Google Street View copy" width="500" height="272" /></a></p>
<p>Later, Galbraith told reporters in Los Angeles that he&#8217;d only wired Stelluto because he didn&#8217;t have any money for food. He needed a stake to get back on his feet.</p>
<p>So what had happened to him?</p>
<p><a title="Galbraith pale AP image by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8515562669/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8530/8515562669_7982094821.jpg" alt="Galbraith pale AP image" width="230" height="435" /></a></p>
<p>&#8220;I blew my top when I was informed I had been relieved. I packed my bag with several suits and came by train, although I have very little recollection of my departure or arrival. I don&#8217;t remember much until I came to here in this hotel. I vaguely recall being in Canton, Ohio and Chicago, but I&#8217;m not sure how I got here or what I did during that week.&#8221; He said he hadn&#8217;t wanted &#8220;to be a burden&#8221; to his wife of daughters. As for the telegram, he supposed that Stelluto, thinking &#8220;he was serving my interests best&#8221; had gone to the Chief of Police. &#8220;Maybe he was serving my best interests. I hope so.&#8221;</p>
<p>Reached at home, his daughter Jean said &#8220;We&#8217;re all very much relieved that Daddy&#8217;s been located. We certainly don&#8217;t feel that he&#8217;ll be a burden on us and we&#8217;re going to send him the money to fly home. I&#8217;m sure he won&#8217;t have trouble finding another job.&#8221;</p>
<p>Galbraith was one of the lucky ones. Many other&nbsp;<a href="http://insroland.org/ghostsofthececil" target="_blank">troubled souls</a>&nbsp;had found a bed at the Cecil and lacked the courage to ask for help. He went home. Reporters, who always want more, asked after him. Jean said that he was somewhat unwell from his travels, and was resting. Jean protected her father well. We hear nothing more about him, and sometimes hearing nothing is the happiest ending of all.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/26/missingconsul/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ghosts of the Cecil</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/25/ghostsofthececil/</link>
		<comments>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/25/ghostsofthececil/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 21:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kim Cooper]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[location tag]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.insroland.org/?p=598</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It was with shock and no small amount of horror that we learned that a body, believed to be that of Canadian tourist Elisa Lam, last seen behaving strangely in an elevator security video recorded on February 1, had been discovered today within one of the water tanks on the Cecil Hotel&#8217;s roof. A complaint &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/25/ghostsofthececil/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Ghosts of the Cecil"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It was with shock and no small amount of horror that we learned that a body, believed to be that of Canadian tourist Elisa Lam, last seen behaving strangely in an elevator security video recorded on February 1, had been discovered today within one of the water tanks on the Cecil Hotel&#8217;s roof. A complaint about low water pressure had prompted an employee to look inside.&nbsp;</p>
<p><a title="Cecil Hotel roof helicopter screen shot february 19 2013 by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8491046418/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8376/8491046418_037307c15e_o.png" alt="Cecil Hotel roof helicopter screen shot february 19 2013" width="618" height="342" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hotels by their nature are the backdrop for extreme behavior, and any public building that stands for the better part of a century will collect its share of tragedies. The Cecil (established 1927) is notable among true crime aficionados as the short-term residence of serial killers Jack Unterweger and Richard Ramirez, and in all the attention paid to those grim gentlemen, the hotel&#8217;s other heartbreaks too often go unmourned.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The probable fate of Miss Lam inspires us to compose a memorial note, to the five prior ladies (and one unfortunate fellow) who left this world on the grounds of the Cecil Hotel, and whose wraiths may yet haunt the place.</p>
<p><a title="hotel-cecil-ad for web by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8491046412/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8366/8491046412_beaa5a459e.jpg" alt="hotel-cecil-ad for web" width="288" height="281" /></a></p>
<p>On June 4, 1964, &#8220;Pigeon Goldie&#8221; Osgood, retired telephone operator and well known protector and feeder of the birds in Pershing Square, was found dead in her room by a hotel worker distributing phone books. She had been stabbed, strangled and raped, and her room ransacked.&nbsp; Near her body were found the Dodgers cap she always wore and a paper sack full of birdseed. Soon after, Jacques B. Ehlinger, 29, was seen walking through Pershing Square in bloodstained clothing. He was arrested, but cleared of the crime, for which no one was ever arrested.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The next day, Goldie&#8217;s friends came together in Pershing Square to express their grief. Jean Rosenstein, a retired nurse, told a reporter &#8220;We were all her friends, all of us here at the square. I was just standing here this morning, thinking about what had happened, when somebody suggested we get some flowers. No one has much money around here, but all of a sudden everyone started giving me what they could. We just wanted her to know we remembered.&#8221;</p>
<p>Pigeon Goldie, we remember you, too.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It was October 12, 1962 and Pauline Otton, 27, had been arguing with her estranged husband Dewey in a room on the ninth floor when he decided he’d had enough and went out to get some dinner. She decided she’d had enough, too, and jumped from the window. She landed on top of a pedestrian, George Gianinni, 65, and both were killed instantly. Since no one saw Pauline jump, police initially thought they had a double suicide on their hands&#8211;but on closer examination, George had his hands in his pockets and was still wearing shoes, which would have been unlikely if he’d fallen ninety feet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pauline, and George, we remember.</p>
<p>On February 11, 1962, Julia Moore climbed out of her eighth floor room window and landed in a second story interior light well. She left no note, just a bus ticket from St. Louis, 59 cents in change, and an Illinois bank book showing a balance of $1800.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Julia, we remember.</p>
<p>On October 22, 1954, Helen Gurnee, 50-something, stepped from her seventh floor window and crashed to her death atop the hotel&#8217;s marquee. She had registered as Margaret Brown a week before.</p>
<p>Helen—or Margaret, as she preferred—we remember.</p>
<p>Elisa Lam, 21, left her home in Vancouver for a solo trip to California. Her plans after visiting Los Angeles were to continue north to Santa Cruz, but it seems that she never left Main Street.</p>
<p>She had the great misfortune to vanish while the Los Angeles Police Department was absorbed with one of the largest manhunts in its history, and one cannot but wonder what impact the search for Christopher Dorner had upon the search for Elisa Lam.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Perhaps she climbed up the side of the water tank, lifted the hatch, slipped inside, drowned, and then floated there for weeks until her body sank and blocked the pipes. Maybe someone who knew the nooks and crannies of this very old establishment put her there. In time, the answer will come, but it will make no great difference. She is gone, and she remains.</p>
<p>Elisa, we remember. And hope the souls that went before can lend some comfort now to yours.</p>
<p><a title="elisa lam in elevator by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8491046290/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8244/8491046290_89d9af45aa_o.jpg" alt="elisa lam in elevator" width="650" height="440" /></a></p>
<p>See also <a href="http://insroland.org/missingconsul" target="_self">The Case of the Missing Consul.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/02/25/ghostsofthececil/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Markup: HTML Tags and Formatting</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/11/markup-html-tags-and-formatting/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 03:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alquin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Markup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[formatting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[html]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[markup]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wptest.io/demo/?p=919</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Headings Header one Header two Header three Header four Header five Header six Blockquotes Single line blockquote: Stay hungry. Stay foolish. Multi line blockquote with a cite reference: People think focus means saying yes to the thing you&#8217;ve got to focus on. But that&#8217;s not what it means at all. It means saying no to &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/11/markup-html-tags-and-formatting/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Markup: HTML Tags and Formatting"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Headings</h2>
<h1>Header one</h1>
<h2>Header two</h2>
<h3>Header three</h3>
<h4>Header four</h4>
<h5>Header five</h5>
<h6>Header six</h6>
<h2>Blockquotes</h2>
<p>Single line blockquote:</p>
<blockquote><p>Stay hungry. Stay foolish.</p></blockquote>
<p>Multi line blockquote with a cite reference:</p>
<blockquote><p>People think focus means saying yes to the thing you&#8217;ve got to focus on. But that&#8217;s not what it means at all. It means saying no to the hundred other good ideas that there are. You have to pick carefully. I&#8217;m actually as proud of the things we haven&#8217;t done as the things I have done. Innovation is saying no to 1,000 things. </p></blockquote>
<p><cite>Steve Jobs</cite> &#8211; Apple Worldwide Developers&#8217; Conference, 1997</p>
<h2>Tables</h2>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Employee</th>
<th>Salary</th>
<th></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<th><a href="http://example.org/">John Doe</a></th>
<td>$1</td>
<td>Because that&#8217;s all Steve Jobs needed for a salary.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<th><a href="http://example.org/">Jane Doe</a></th>
<td>$100K</td>
<td>For all the blogging she does.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<th><a href="http://example.org/">Fred Bloggs</a></th>
<td>$100M</td>
<td>Pictures are worth a thousand words, right? So Jane x 1,000.</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<th><a href="http://example.org/">Jane Bloggs</a></th>
<td>$100B</td>
<td>With hair like that?! Enough said&#8230;</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h2>Definition Lists</h2>
<dl>
<dt>Definition List Title</dt>
<dd>Definition list division.</dd>
<dt>Startup</dt>
<dd>A startup company or startup is a company or temporary organization designed to search for a repeatable and scalable business model.</dd>
<dt>#dowork</dt>
<dd>Coined by Rob Dyrdek and his personal body guard Christopher &#8220;Big Black&#8221; Boykins, &#8220;Do Work&#8221; works as a self motivator, to motivating your friends.</dd>
<dt>Do It Live</dt>
<dd>I&#8217;ll let Bill O&#8217;Reilly will <a title="We'll Do It Live" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O_HyZ5aW76c">explain</a> this one.</dd>
</dl>
<h2>Unordered Lists (Nested)</h2>
<ul>
<li>List item one
<ul>
<li>List item one
<ul>
<li>List item one</li>
<li>List item two</li>
<li>List item three</li>
<li>List item four</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>List item two</li>
<li>List item three</li>
<li>List item four</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>List item two</li>
<li>List item three</li>
<li>List item four</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ordered List (Nested)</h2>
<ol>
<li>List item one
<ol>
<li>List item one
<ol>
<li>List item one</li>
<li>List item two</li>
<li>List item three</li>
<li>List item four</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>List item two</li>
<li>List item three</li>
<li>List item four</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>List item two</li>
<li>List item three</li>
<li>List item four</li>
</ol>
<h2>HTML Tags</h2>
<p>These supported tags come from the WordPress.com code <a title="Code" href="http://en.support.wordpress.com/code/">FAQ</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Address Tag</strong></p>
<address>1 Infinite Loop<br />
Cupertino, CA 95014<br />
United States</address>
<p><strong>Anchor Tag (aka. Link)</strong></p>
<p>This is an example of a <a title="Apple" href="http://apple.com/">link</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Abbreviation Tag</strong></p>
<p>The abbreviation <abbr title="Seriously">srsly</abbr> stands for &#8220;seriously&#8221;.</p>
<p><strong>Acronym Tag (<em>deprecated in HTML5</em>)</strong></p>
<p>The acronym <acronym title="For The Win">ftw</acronym> stands for &#8220;for the win&#8221;.</p>
<p><strong>Big Tag <strong>(<em>deprecated in HTML5</em>)</strong></strong></p>
<p>These tests are a <big>big</big> deal, but this tag is no longer supported in HTML5.</p>
<p><strong>Cite Tag</strong></p>
<p>&#8220;Code is poetry.&#8221; &#8212;<cite>Automattic</cite></p>
<p><strong>Code Tag</strong></p>
<p>You will learn later on in these tests that <code>word-wrap: break-word;</code> will be your best friend.</p>
<p><strong>Delete Tag</strong></p>
<p>This tag will let you <del>strikeout text</del>, but this tag is no longer supported in HTML5 (use the <code>&lt;strike&gt;</code> instead).</p>
<p><strong>Emphasize Tag</strong></p>
<p>The emphasize tag should <em>italicize</em> text.</p>
<p><strong>Insert Tag</strong></p>
<p>This tag should denote <ins>inserted</ins> text.</p>
<p><strong>Keyboard Tag</strong></p>
<p>This scarcely known tag emulates <kbd>keyboard text</kbd>, which is usually styled like the <code>&lt;code&gt;</code> tag.</p>
<p><strong>Preformatted Tag</strong></p>
<p>This tag styles large blocks of code.</p>
<pre>.post-title {
	margin: 0 0 5px;
	font-weight: bold;
	font-size: 38px;
	line-height: 1.2;
	and here's a line of some really, really, really, really long text, just to see how the PRE tag handles it and to find out how it overflows;
}</pre>
<p><strong>Quote Tag</strong></p>
<p><q>Developers, developers, developers&#8230;</q> &#8211;Steve Ballmer</p>
<p><strong>Strike Tag <strong>(<em>deprecated in HTML5</em>)</strong></strong></p>
<p>This tag shows <span style="text-decoration:line-through;">strike-through text</span></p>
<p><strong>Strong Tag</strong></p>
<p>This tag shows <strong>bold<strong> text.</strong></strong></p>
<p><strong>Subscript Tag</strong></p>
<p>Getting our science styling on with H<sub>2</sub>O, which should push the &#8220;2&#8221; down.</p>
<p><strong>Superscript Tag</strong></p>
<p>Still sticking with science and Isaac Newton&#8217;s E = MC<sup>2</sup>, which should lift the 2 up.</p>
<p><strong>Teletype Tag <strong>(<em>deprecated in HTML5</em>)</strong></strong></p>
<p>This rarely used tag emulates <tt>teletype text</tt>, which is usually styled like the <code>&lt;code&gt;</code> tag.</p>
<p><strong>Variable Tag</strong></p>
<p>This allows you to denote <var>variables</var>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Markup: Image Alignment</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/10/markup-image-alignment/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alquin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Markup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alignment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[captions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[image]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[markup]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wptest.io/demo/?p=903</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let&#8217;s get started. On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options of None, Left, Right, and Center. In &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/10/markup-image-alignment/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Markup: Image Alignment"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let&#8217;s get started.</p>
<p>On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options of <em>None</em>, <em>Left</em>, <em>Right, </em>and <em>Center</em>. In addition, they also get the options of <em>Thumbnail</em>, <em>Medium</em>, <em>Large</em> &amp; <em>Fullsize</em>.</p>
<p style="text-align:center;"><img class="size-full wp-image-906 aligncenter" title="Image Alignment 580x300" alt="Image Alignment 580x300" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg" width="580" height="300" /></p>
<p>The image above happens to be <em><strong>centered</strong></em>.</p>
<p><strong><img class="size-full wp-image-904 alignleft" title="Image Alignment 150x150" alt="Image Alignment 150x150" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg" width="150" height="150" /></strong>The rest of this paragraph is filler for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150&#215;150 image, which is <em><strong>left aligned</strong></em>. <strong></strong></p>
<p>As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one more sentence here, we&#8217;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image in seamless transition. Again, letting the do it&#8217;s thang. Mission accomplished!</p>
<p>And now for a <em><strong>massively large image</strong></em>. It also has <em><strong>no alignment</strong></em>.</p>
<p><img class="alignnone  wp-image-907" title="Image Alignment 1200x400" alt="Image Alignment 1200x400" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg" width="1200" height="400" /></p>
<p>The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.</p>
<p><img class="size-full wp-image-905 alignright" title="Image Alignment 300x200" alt="Image Alignment 300x200" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg" width="300" height="200" /></p>
<p>And now we&#8217;re going to shift things to the <em><strong>right align</strong></em>. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there&#8230; Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&#8217;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&#8217;t let anyone else tell you differently.</p>
<p>In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah&#8230; Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.</p>
<p>And just when you thought we were done, we&#8217;re going to do them all over again with captions!</p>
<figure id="attachment_906" style="width: 580px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-906  " title="Image Alignment 580x300" alt="Image Alignment 580x300" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg" width="580" height="300" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Look at 580&#215;300 getting some <a title="Image Settings" href="http://en.support.wordpress.com/images/image-settings/">caption</a> love.</figcaption></figure>
<p>The image above happens to be <em><strong>centered</strong></em>. The caption also has a link in it, just to see if it does anything funky.</p>
<figure id="attachment_904" style="width: 150px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img class="size-full wp-image-904  " title="Image Alignment 150x150" alt="Image Alignment 150x150" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg" width="150" height="150" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Itty-bitty caption.</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong></strong>The rest of this paragraph is filler for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150&#215;150 image, which is <em><strong>left aligned</strong></em>. <strong></strong></p>
<p>As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one more sentence here, we&#8217;ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image in seamless transition. Again, letting the do it&#8217;s thang. Mission accomplished!</p>
<p>And now for a <em><strong>massively large image</strong></em>. It also has <em><strong>no alignment</strong></em>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_907" style="width: 1200px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class=" wp-image-907" title="Image Alignment 1200x400" alt="Image Alignment 1200x400" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg" width="1200" height="400" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Massive image comment for your eyeballs.</figcaption></figure>
<p>The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.</p>
<figure id="attachment_905" style="width: 300px" class="wp-caption alignright"><img class="size-full wp-image-905 " title="Image Alignment 300x200" alt="Image Alignment 300x200" src="http://alquin.testingrichardsdomains.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg" width="300" height="200" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Feels good to be right all the time.</figcaption></figure>
<p>And now we&#8217;re going to shift things to the <em><strong>right align</strong></em>. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there&#8230; Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don&#8217;t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don&#8217;t let anyone else tell you differently.</p>
<p>In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah&#8230; Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.</p>
<p>And that&#8217;s a wrap, yo! You survived the tumultuous waters of alignment. Image alignment achievement unlocked!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Markup: Text Alignment</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/09/markup-text-alignment/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 16:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alquin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Markup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alignment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[content]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[markup]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wptest.io/demo/?p=895</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Default This is a paragraph. It should not have any alignment of any kind. It should just flow like you would normally expect. Nothing fancy. Just straight up text, free flowing, with love. Completely neutral and not picking a side or sitting on the fence. It just is. It just freaking is. It likes where &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/09/markup-text-alignment/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Markup: Text Alignment"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Default</h3>
<p>This is a paragraph. It should not have any alignment of any kind. It should just flow like you would normally expect. Nothing fancy. Just straight up text, free flowing, with love. Completely neutral and not picking a side or sitting on the fence. It just is. It just freaking is. It likes where it is. It does not feel compelled to pick a side. Leave him be. It will just be better that way. Trust me.</p>
<h3>Left Align</h3>
<p style="text-align:left;">This is a paragraph. It is left aligned. Because of this, it is a bit more liberal in it&#8217;s views. It&#8217;s favorite color is green. Left align tends to be more eco-friendly, but it provides no concrete evidence that it really is. Even though it likes share the wealth evenly, it leaves the equal distribution up to justified alignment.</p>
<h3>Center Align</h3>
<p style="text-align:center;">This is a paragraph. It is center aligned. Center is, but nature, a fence sitter. A flip flopper. It has a difficult time making up its mind. It wants to pick a side. Really, it does. It has the best intentions, but it tends to complicate matters more than help. The best you can do is try to win it over and hope for the best. I hear center align does take bribes.</p>
<h3>Right Align</h3>
<p style="text-align:right;">This is a paragraph. It is right aligned. It is a bit more conservative in it&#8217;s views. It&#8217;s prefers to not be told what to do or how to do it. Right align totally owns a slew of guns and loves to head to the range for some practice. Which is cool and all. I mean, it&#8217;s a pretty good shot from at least four or five football fields away. Dead on. So boss.</p>
<h3>Justify Align</h3>
<p style="text-align:justify;">This is a paragraph. It is justify aligned. It gets really mad when people associate it with Justin Timberlake. Typically, justified is pretty straight laced. It likes everything to be in it&#8217;s place and not all cattywampus like the rest of the aligns. I am not saying that makes it better than the rest of the aligns, but it does tend to put off more of an elitist attitude.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Markup: Title With Special Characters</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/05/title-with-special-characters/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 18:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alquin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Markup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[html]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[markup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[post]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[title]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wptest.io/demo/?p=867</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Putting special characters in the title should have no adverse effect on the layout or functionality. Special characters in the post title have been known to cause issues with JavaScript when it is minified, especially in the admin when editing the post itself (ie. issues with metaboxes, media upload, etc.). Latin Character Tests This is &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/05/title-with-special-characters/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Markup: Title With Special Characters"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Putting special characters in the title should have no adverse effect on the layout or functionality.</p>
<p>Special characters in the post title have been known to cause issues with JavaScript when it is minified, especially in the admin when editing the post itself (ie. issues with metaboxes, media upload, etc.).</p>
<h2>Latin Character Tests</h2>
<p>This is a test to see if the fonts used in this theme support basic Latin characters.</p>
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>!</td>
<td>&#8220;</td>
<td>#</td>
<td>$</td>
<td>%</td>
<td>&amp;</td>
<td>&#8216;</td>
<td>(</td>
<td>)</td>
<td>*</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>+</td>
<td>,</td>
<td>&#8211;</td>
<td>.</td>
<td>/</td>
<td>0</td>
<td>1</td>
<td>2</td>
<td>3</td>
<td>4</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>5</td>
<td>6</td>
<td>7</td>
<td>8</td>
<td>9</td>
<td>:</td>
<td>;</td>
<td>&gt;</td>
<td>=</td>
<td>&lt;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>?</td>
<td>@</td>
<td>A</td>
<td>B</td>
<td>C</td>
<td>D</td>
<td>E</td>
<td>F</td>
<td>G</td>
<td>H</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>I</td>
<td>J</td>
<td>K</td>
<td>L</td>
<td>M</td>
<td>N</td>
<td>O</td>
<td>P</td>
<td>Q</td>
<td>R</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>S</td>
<td>T</td>
<td>U</td>
<td>V</td>
<td>W</td>
<td>X</td>
<td>Y</td>
<td>Z</td>
<td>[</td>
<td>\</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>]</td>
<td>^</td>
<td>_</td>
<td>`</td>
<td>a</td>
<td>b</td>
<td>c</td>
<td>d</td>
<td>e</td>
<td>f</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>g</td>
<td>h</td>
<td>i</td>
<td>j</td>
<td>k</td>
<td>l</td>
<td>m</td>
<td>n</td>
<td>o</td>
<td>p</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>q</td>
<td>r</td>
<td>s</td>
<td>t</td>
<td>u</td>
<td>v</td>
<td>w</td>
<td>x</td>
<td>y</td>
<td>z</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>{</td>
<td>|</td>
<td>}</td>
<td>~</td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
<td></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Markup: Title With Markup</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2013/01/05/markup-title-with-markup/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alquin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Markup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[css]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[html]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[title]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://wptest.io/demo/?p=861</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Verify that: The post title renders the word &#8220;with&#8221; in italics and the word &#8220;markup&#8221; in bold. The post title markup should be removed from the browser window / tab.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Verify that:</p>
<ul>
<li><span style="line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;">The post title renders the word &#8220;with&#8221; in </span><em style="line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;">italics</em><span style="line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;"> and the word &#8220;markup&#8221; in </span><strong style="line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;">bold</strong><span style="line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;">.</span></li>
<li><span style="line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;">The post title markup should be removed from the browser window / tab.</span></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleuthing A Presidential Mystery in Downtown Los Angeles</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/28/kingedwardandtr/</link>
		<comments>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/28/kingedwardandtr/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rss]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[location tag]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.insroland.org/?p=613</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Should you step into the lobby of the King Edward Hotel at the corner of 5th and Los Angeles Streets in L.A.&#8217;s historic Skid Row, and pause to admire the black and gold Egyptian marble fixtures, ionic columns and sweeping mezzanine stair, the odds are better than good that the fellow behind the counter will &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/28/kingedwardandtr/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Sleuthing A Presidential Mystery in Downtown Los Angeles"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Should you step into the lobby of the King Edward Hotel at the corner of 5<sup>th</sup> and Los Angeles Streets in L.A.&#8217;s historic Skid Row, and pause to admire the black and gold Egyptian marble fixtures, ionic columns and sweeping mezzanine stair, the odds are better than good that the fellow behind the counter will draw your attention to the clock above the desk and the fancy raised initials just below it.</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Hotel IMG_4833 for blog by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229267892/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8208/8229267892_caf72d5850_z.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel IMG_4833 for blog" width="428" height="640"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>And in answer to your predictable question, he&#8217;ll reply: &#8220;Teddy Roosevelt! He stayed here when he visited Los Angeles.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Hotel IMG_4833 TR crop by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229267338/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8069/8229267338_e5e03ce678_z.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel IMG_4833 TR crop" width="579" height="332"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Presidential sleepover would be a point of pride for any establishment&#8211;all the more so in a young city in the far west. How marvelous a fact, and no wonder the King Eddy&#8217;s staff is so quick to share it. (We&#8217;ve confirmed that this information has been passed down through oral tradition since at least the mid-1970s.)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Hotel fiesta pinback 1903 by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8228198577/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8340/8228198577_5c3ac0c27f_m.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel fiesta pinback 1903" width="220" height="221"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>There&#8217;s only one problem. Theodore Roosevelt&#8217;s famous visit to Los Angeles was on May 8, 1903. He attended the Fiesta de las Flores parade, and stayed that night at the fashionable&nbsp;<a href="http://insroland.org/annasvoices" target="_blank">Westminster Hotel</a>&nbsp;at 4<sup>th</sup> and Main Streets, two blocks away.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Hotel May 9 1903 LAT page 45 Roosevelt at Fiesta screen grab by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229265802/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8478/8229265802_f3ee304cbf_z.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel May 9 1903 LAT page 45 Roosevelt at Fiesta screen grab" width="470" height="544"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The King Edward didn&#8217;t open until 1906.</p>
<p>Oh, but then Roosevelt must have stayed at the King Edward on a later tour of the Southland, right?</p>
<p>Well, historical records do show that Roosevelt return once more to Los Angeles, for two days in March 1911, when the ex-President spoke at Occidental College and Throop Polytechnic.</p>
<p>His stay at Pasadena&#8217;s <a href="http://www.pasadenaweekly.com/cms/story/detail/a_world_unto_itself/11309/" target="_blank">Hotel Maryland</a> was well publicized, and included a <a href="http://www.pe.com/local-news/riverside-county/riverside/riverside-headlines-index/20111217-riverside-ex-president-roosevelt-meets-former-slave.ece" target="_blank">poignant meeting</a> with an aged slave who had been owned by Roosevelt&#8217;s maternal family in Antebellum Georgia.</p>
<p>But there appears to be no documentation of a stop at the King Edward or any other Los Angeles hotel.</p>
<p>So why in the name of all that&#8217;s historical are the initials T.R. stuck up above the desk of the King Edward Hotel today?</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve been wracking our brains, and have come up with a few theories worth floating.</p>
<p>Perhaps before the Westminster Hotel&nbsp;fell to the wrecking ball in 1960, someone went to the auction and bid on a piece of commemorative marble, transporting the legend of a Presidential visit along with the physical artifact back to the nearby establishment?</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Hotel Westminster roosevelt slept here wrecking by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229265516/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8488/8229265516_1c7d0b68a8_z.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel Westminster roosevelt slept here wrecking" width="547" height="388"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>A tempting notion, but a rare 1920s-era promotional map printed by the King Edward includes a photo of the lobby, which while printed using the halftone technique which makes it impossible to &#8220;zoom in&#8221; and see finer details, certainly appears to already show a set of initials there beneath the clock.</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Lobby circa 1920 from our map watermark by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229265942/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8202/8229265942_7d8a180f47_z.jpg" alt="King Edward Lobby circa 1920 from our map watermark" width="640" height="297"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;
</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&lt;<a title="King Edward Hotel clock detail circa 1920 by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229303910/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8489/8229303910_b62cc2f18a.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel clock detail circa 1920" width="396" height="349"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Well, could they represent an owner of the hotel? The King Edward was built by architect John Parkinson and operated in its early years by Colonel E. Dunham, Tommy Law and Thomas L. Dodge. Not a &#8220;T.R.&#8221; in the bunch.</p>
<p>Having weighed and sorted these and other, less reasonable, possibilities, we&#8217;re prepared to come down on the side of one unsupportable, but eminently pragmatic solution: that the patriotic initials are merely a tip of the hat to a popular politician, and an answer to any testy patron who might question the red-blooded Americanism of a hotel named for a foreign king.</p>
<p>We reckon that&#8217;s as good a theory as any, and we&#8217;re sticking with it until and unless something better comes along.</p>
<p>Which leaves the initials &#8220;T.R.&#8221; above the desk of the King Edward, and the abiding oral tradition of the great man&#8217;s visit, something of a mystery&#8211;but no less beguiling for that. Since everyone who knew the real answer is dead, we&#8217;re free to craft our own myths to pass along to Angelenos who&#8217;ll come after. Why do <em>you</em> believe the initials &#8220;T.R.&#8221; are there under the clock in the King Eddy?</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><a title="King Edward Hotel TR marches in King Edward VII funeral procession May 20 1910 Library of Congress by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8229265682/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8063/8229265682_4d4a3db5e1_z.jpg" alt="King Edward Hotel TR marches in King Edward VII funeral procession May 20 1910 Library of Congress" width="640" height="533"/></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>This meditation on time and memory was written on the occasion of the upcoming shuttering of the&nbsp;</em><a href="http://lavatransforms.org/finalblowoutkingeddy" target="_blank">King Edward Saloon</a><em>&nbsp;and the auction of its equipment and memorabilia.</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/28/kingedwardandtr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Los Angeles Prosperity Carnival and Indoor Fair of 1915</title>
		<link>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/12/prosper/</link>
		<comments>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/12/prosper/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 03:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rss]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[location tag]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.insroland.org/?p=614</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s a thrilling bit of lost Los Angeles lore worth shining a torch on: after San Francisco&#8217;s celebrated Panama-Pacific International Exposition folded up its tents in late 1915, clever promoter H.W. Nixon brought quite a number of the midway attractions from &#8220;The Zone, the Street of Fun&#8221; down to Broadway, where they filled the old &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/12/prosper/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "The Los Angeles Prosperity Carnival and Indoor Fair of 1915"</span></a></p>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Here&#8217;s a thrilling bit of lost Los Angeles lore worth shining a torch on: after San Francisco&#8217;s celebrated <a href="http://www.sfmuseum.org/hist9/ppietxt1.html">Panama-Pacific International Exposition</a> folded up its tents in late 1915, clever promoter H.W. Nixon brought quite a number of the midway attractions from <a href="/web/20160307123451/http://www.sanfranciscomemories.com/ppie/zone.html"> &#8220;The Zone, the Street of Fun&#8221;</a> down to Broadway, where they filled the old Boston Store building.</p>
<p><a title="boston dry goods store facade by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182614806/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8202/8182614806_6debb09299_c.jpg" alt="boston dry goods store facade" width="581" height="800" /></a></p>
<p>The Boston was the department store founded by the Robinson family; the building, missing its upper stories, today houses a wedding chapel.</p>
<p>&lt;<a title="toyland on the zone 17731 by richardschave, on Flickr" href="/http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182615626/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8063/8182615626_2e13a78a9e.jpg" alt="toyland on the zone 17731" width="500" height="249" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Some of the daffiness to be found on &#8220;The Zone.&#8221;</em></p>
<p>The Los Angeles Prosperity Carnival and Indoor Fair opened at 6pm on Saturday, December 11 to an audience of 5000 eager souls, and for the next 30 days, there was no place more amusing &#8212; or peculiar &#8212; in all the southland.</p>
<p><a title="opening festivities LA Times by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182615348/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8200/8182615348_676d83e4e1_o.png" alt="opening festivities LA Times" width="682" height="608" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Huge crowd celebrates the opening of the festivities. Photo: LA Times</em></p>
<p>The fair began with the &#8220;wedding&#8221; of Mr. Midget (real name: Lajos Matina, one of the Hungarian Matina triplets, all later <em>Wizard of Oz</em>&nbsp;Munchkins) to Miss Midget (Elise Broek). The couple were residents of Midget City, whose troupe appeared under the leadership of Prince Ludwig, whose professional bio had him a wee member of European royalty. Miss Midget, by the by, was a suffragette.</p>
<p><a title="Prince Ludwig (Chicago Tribune) by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182613478/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8350/8182613478_810fc50f9a_o.jpg" alt="Prince Ludwig (Chicago Tribune)" width="500" height="380" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Prince Ludwig addresses his subjects at Midget Village, an attraction at the 1933 World&#8217;s Fair. Photo: Chicago Tribune</em></p>
<p>Prize rabbits and pigeons by the hundreds were exhibited, with Los Angeles husbandry clubs competing against those fuddyduds in Pasadena.</p>
<p><a title="blanche payson colliers 1915 by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182577627/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8486/8182577627_698fcd6b9c_o.gif" alt="blanche payson colliers 1915" width="111" height="350" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Officer Payson at the PPIE, where she protected lady fairgoers from mashers. Photo: Collier&#8217;s.</em></p>
<p>Like large ladies in uniform? (Who doesn&#8217;t?) Then you won&#8217;t want to miss an audience with Mrs. Blanche Payson, popular 6&#8217;4&#8243; PPIE policewoman, who was on display in her cute &#8220;coppette&#8221; garb. You can still enjoy Mrs. Payson in some classic short <a href="http://www.lordheath.com/index.php?p=1_278_Blanche-Payson">comedies.</a></p>
<p>Hold your nose on the third floor, where a grand cat show, organized by the Los Angeles Cat Fanciers Association, featured prize-winning kitties from overseas and around the country.</p>
<p><a title="Turkish Harem by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182577331/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8202/8182577331_e3a5907c1c_o.jpg" alt="Turkish Harem" width="550" height="739" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Some of the pretties on display. Photo: LA Times.</em></p>
<p>The fifth floor was transformed into an Oriental Village staffed with young lovelies, each of them a &#8220;real Egyptian princess&#8221; and a talented dancer. They also had a pet serpent named Zoo, and Turkish cigarettes and water pipes available for male visitors to sample. This show was developed for the 1893 Chicago World&#8217;s Fair and had been touring ever since.</p>
<p>&#8220;In Old Hawaii,&#8221; a song and dance show, was considered one of the higher-class attractions of the fair.</p>
<p><a title="siamese twins by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182615538/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8337/8182615538_c5bb00ddf2.jpg" alt="siamese twins" width="267" height="400" /></a></p>
<p>Then there was a Human Fish, who appeared to eat, drink and sleep inside his tank. And a chance to coo at the three-year-old Cuban-born Siamese <a href="http://phreeque.tripod.com/hinojosa_twins.html">twins</a>&nbsp;Josephina and Guadalupe Hinojosa.</p>
<p>But wait, there&#8217;s more! All the way from Van Nuys come&#8230; (wait for it)&#8230; 500 high-class chickens. Under the direction of W.P. Whitsett of the Chamber of Commerce, locals brought their best birds to show off the suitability of the SFV as a center of chicken ranching. The first such ranch opened just three years ago, and by 1915 there are 150 of them. The aim was to &#8220;make Van Nuys the Petaluma of Southern California.&#8221; Favorite entrants included Lord Roselawn I, a majestic White Leghorn rooster and Sport, a Barred Plymouth Rock. Also on view: fighting cocks who battled in cages.</p>
<p>And for the kiddies, Santa distributed gifts beneath one of the largest Christmas trees ever brought to Los Angeles.</p>
<p>One of the weirdest elements of the fair was the Baby Bollinger Show, a wax replica of the malformed Chicago infant whose <a href="http://www.waragainsttheweak.com/offSiteArchive/HitlerDebtToAmerica.html" target="_blank">death</a> the previous month had been national news. Allan Bollinger had the misfortune to be under the &#8220;care&#8221; of Dr. Harry Haiselden, a proponent of euthanasia and eugenics who not only convinced the boy&#8217;s parents to let their &#8220;sure-to-become-a-criminal&#8221; infant die rather than attempt any lifesaving surgeries, but actively sought media attention for doing so. The controversy over the Bollinger case led an ethics complaint against Haiselden, who would later star in an autobiographical pro-eugenics film called <em><a href="http://www.npr.org/programs/disability/ba_shows.dir/children.dir/highlights/bsmovsti.html" target="_blank">The Black Stork.</a></em></p>
<p><a title="101 Ranch WENONA (1913) Half-Sheet by richardschave, on Flickr" href="/web/20160307123451/http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182577111/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8057/8182577111_902ec4c644_c.jpg" alt="101 Ranch WENONA (1913) Half-Sheet" width="518" height="800" /></a></p>
<p>And then there was Princess Wenona with her Miniature Wild West Show.  Princess Wenona, previously called Lillian Smith, perched atop her piebald pony Rabbit, was a star marksman in the 101 Ranch wild west show and had appeared with Buffalo Bill Cody in the 1880s.   Her theatrical back story claimed that her mother was kidnapped by Sioux Indians, and that Lillian was the result of a liaison with Crazy Snake, a chief.</p>
<p>She was of Indian ancestry, just not from the Plains. In fact, she was born in Coleville, near the California-Nevada border. At 7 she got her first rifle, and became the terror of the Yosemite bird population. In her teens she joined the Buffalo Bill show and played to crowds of up to 200,000 in Staten Island, NY.</p>
<p><a title="Jim_&amp;_Lillian by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182575517/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8069/8182575517_5cbc11757f_o.jpg" alt="Jim_&amp;_Lillian" width="618" height="474" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Lillian Smith on the road, with performer friends and her rifle collection.</em></p>
<p>She was billed as &#8220;The California Huntress,&#8221; &#8220;Champion Girl Rifle Shot&#8221; and &#8220;The California Girl,&#8221; and a prize of $10,000 was offered to anyone who could out shoot Princess Wenona. They say nobody ever claimed that prize.</p>
<p>She had a great rivalry with the established performer Annie Oakley, who began lying about her age as Wenona&#8217;s star ascended. In 1887, both women performed in England on the same bill. At a special performance for the Queen, it is said that Victoria rose for the first time in her life to salute the American flag. While in London, Oakley quarreled with Bill Cody and left the show, leaving Wenona the sole star lady sharpshooter, until Oakley and Cody made up.</p>
<p><a title="geronimo with princess wenona by richardschave, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/richardschave/8182614540/"><img src="http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8070/8182614540_34ec8a308b_c.jpg" alt="geronimo with princess wenona" width="800" height="641" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: right;"><em>Above: Princess Wenona with Buffalo Bill Cody and the famous Apache leader Geronimo, 1901</em></p>
<p>In later years she became rather plump, drank too much and had several unhappy marriages, so by the time she played the Prosperity Carnival, we can assume she was not the star she&#8217;d been. Still, such tricks as shooting out a candle flame or the ashes off a man&#8217;s cigar remained crowd pleasers.</p>
<p>She retired around 1925 and lived out her days on a ranch in Oklahoma with many former Wild West Show friends and dozens of stray dogs that she cared for. She died during the bitter cold winter of 1930, aged 59.</p>
<p>And these are just a few of the more than 150 shows and 200 concessions on display at the Los Angeles Prosperity Carnival and Indoor Fair. Don&#8217;t you wish you could have seen them all?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://www.testingrichardsdomains.com/2012/11/12/prosper/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
